<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WaikatoPapers</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="action_sort_date">latest</string>
    <string name="ic_menu_price_desc">Long to short</string>
    <string name="title_activity_papers_list">PapersListActivity</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">drawer_open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">drawer_close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_paper_details">PaperDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="paper_content_sample">15 Points\n
                \n
                This paper will consider the design and implementation of applications for mobile devices covering topics such as: mobile application software architectures; development platform options; design and evaluation of small-screen touch-based user interfaces; leveraging technologies such as global positioning, near-field communication and orientation/environmental sensing; mobile web applications. Practical work will use the Android platform and so the paper is best-suited to students with experience of Java programming.\n
                \n
                Pre Requisite Papers\n
                60 points at 300 level in Computer Science\n
                \n
                Corresponding Papers\n
                COMP448 Developing Mobile Applications\n
                \n
                Lecturers and Tutors\n
                A Semester\n
                \n
                Lecturer(s)\n
                \n
                Associate Professor Steve Jones \n
                Room: G.2.24\n
                Phone: +64 7 838 4490\n
                stevej@waikato.ac.nz\n
                \n
                Timetable\n
                Official Timetable Information\n
                \n
                Compulsory Components\n
                All items of assessment are compulsory.\n
                \n
                Workload\n
                Approximately 8 hours per week.\n
                \n
                Required Reading\n
                None\n
                \n
                Recommended Reading\n
                Optional but a useful resource: a subscription to http://commonsware.com\n
                \n
                Means of Assessment\n
                4 practical software development tasks.\n
                \n
                Assessment Ratio\n
                Internal assessment/final examination ratio 1:0\n
                \n
                Assessment Components\n
                There are 4 items of coursework. Each is worth one quarter of the final course grade. Submission dates are as follows:\n
                \n
                Coursework 1: Friday 27th March\n
                Coursework 2: Friday 8th May\n
                Coursework 3: Monday 8th June\n
                Coursework 4: Wednesday 10th June\n
                Coursework will be practically oriented and focus on design and implementation of a mobile application.\n
                Hand in and Return of Assignments\n
                Assignments will be submitted electronically via Moodle. Grades and feedback will be returned via Moodle.\n
                \n
                Attendance Policy\n
                Class attendance is expected. The course notes provided are not comprehensive, additional material will be covered in class. You are responsible for all material covered in class.\n
                \n
                Lecture Outlines\n
                See Moodle page.\n
                \n
                Changes in Response to Course Evaluations\n
                Coursework 1 modified to place more emphasis on implementation rather than UI design.\n
                \n
                Academic Integrity\n
                Follow this link for Academic Integrity information and this link for detailed explanation of How to prevent plagiarism in Computer Science assessment items.\n
                \n
                Performance Impairment\n
                Follow this link for information on Performance Impairment.\n
                \n
                Student Concerns and Complaints\n
                Follow this link for Student Concerns and Complaints information.\n
                \n
                Application for Extension\n
                Follow this link for information on applying for an Extension.\n
                \n
                Review of Grade\n
                Follow this link for information on applying for a Review of Grade.\n
                \n
                University Regulations\n
                Your attention is drawn to the following regulations and policies, which are published in the University Calendar:\n
                \n
                Assessment Regulations 2005\n
                Student Discipline Regulations 2008\n
                Computer Systems Regulations 2005\n
                Policy on the Use of Māori for Assessment\n
                Ethical Conduct in Human Research and Related Activities Regulations 2008\n
                Student Research Regulations 2008</string>
</resources>
